{
  "questions": [ 
       {
           "question": "1.1 Capacidades instaladas",
           "answers": ["True", "False"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "1.2 Contrapartes definidas",
           "answers": ["True", "False"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Definición de marcos metodológicos"?",
           "answers": ["assignment", "instantiation", "declaration", "iteration"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },

       {
           "question": "4. Conformación sistemas de planificación",
           "answers": ["a constant", "a variable", "a literal", "an object"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "5. Sistemas de apoyo al proceso de planificación",
           "answers": ["byte", "char", "boolean", "short"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "6. Distinción y complementariedad entre plan de gobierno y plan de desarrollo",
           "answers": ["+=", "&&", "!", "||"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "7. Instancias de participación",
           "answers": ["stop();", "end;", "break;", "exit();"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "8. Diseño de indicadores de línea base",
           "answers": ["True", "False", "null", "zero"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "9. Diseño sistema de seguimiento y monitoreo",
           "answers": ["when at least one preceding \"if\" or \"else if\" statement has returned false", 
           "when all preceding \"if\" and \"else if\" statements have returned true", 
           "always regardless of what previous statements have returned", 
           "when all preceding \"if\" and \"else if\" statements have returned false"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       },
       {
           "question": "W ere: i++;",
           "answers": ["assigning", "concatenating", "incrementing", "decrementing"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": " ic?",
           "answers": ["percentage", "remainder", "product", "factor"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": " )",
           "answers": ["a number greater than or equal to zero", "an object reference", 
           "an expression that returns a value of true or false", "a primitive type variable"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 3
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following always starts an infinite while loop?",
           "answers": ["while(true) ", "while(num<0)", "while(;;)", "while(count==0)"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 1
       },
       {
           "question": "How many times will the following for loop execute: for(int i=0; i<=10; i++) { System.out.println(i); }",
           "answers": ["10", "11", "1", "0"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 2
       },
       {
           "question": "Which of the following data types cannot be used as the expression in a switch statement?",
           "answers": ["char", "Integer", "short", "Object"],
       	   "correctAnswer": 4
       } 
     ]
 }
